Everyone loves a happy ending.
Don Jon is a romance, comedy, drama film directed by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
A New Jersey guy dedicated to his family, friends, and church, develops unrealistic expectations from
watching porn and works to find happiness and intimacy with his potential true love.
Jon Martello, Jr., played by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Barbara Sugarman, played by Scarlett Johansson.
Esther, played by Julianne Moore.
Jon Martello, Sr., played by Tony Danza.
Angela Martello, played by Glenne Headly.
Monica Martello, played by Brie Larson.
Don Jon is a 2013 American romantic comedy-drama film written and directed by
Joseph Gordon-Levitt in his feature-length directorial debut.
It stars Gordon-Levitt, Scarlett Johansson, and Julianne Moore.
The supporting cast includes Rob Brown, Glenne
Headly, Brie Larson, and Tony Danza.
The film follows a man whose porn addiction gives him unrealistic romantic and sexual expectations,
prompting him to search for happiness and intimacy with his potential true love.
Don Jon premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on January 18, 2013, and was
released by Relativity Media in the United States on September 27.
It grossed $41 million worldwide on a budget of $3–5.5 million and
received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of pornography, new jersey, sex
addiction, sexual fantasy, internet porn.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.